searchengineoptimising.com 2008-05-09

# Privacy

**Introduction**  
We believe that it is important you know how we treat the information about you that we receive on the Internet. Our privacy statement as set forth below is written so that you can understand exactly what we do and don't do with your information.  
While we will never share information that may be used to identify you, we do expect our policy statement will change as new ways to protect your confidentiality and new uses for information emerge. To that end, we value your comments about our privacy statement and invite you to contact us with suggestions and concerns. 

**Information Collection & Use**  
_Registration_  
In general, you may visit the Site without telling us who you are or revealing any personally identifiable information about you. To place an order on this Web site, you can complete the registration form and create a password. During registration you are required to give contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest. 

If you choose to register you will be able to access the additional features of our site such as view your order history, post in forums and write reviews.

_When you register we will send you an email confirming your account has been created._

SEO (a trading style of Babylon Technologies Ltd) is the sole owner of the information collected on searchengineoptimising.com. SEO collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Web site.

_Orders_  
If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). 

None of your personal financial information (such as a credit card number and expiration date) is stored by us. Therefore it is impossible for it to be sold or rented to any party for secondary purposes. Worldpay, owed by The Royal Bank of Scotland, provide a gateway which allows SEO customers to securely pay for goods ordered from our web site. The security and privacy of all card details are maintained by Worldpay high levels of encryption, (SSL, 128-bit encryption, the highest level of protection possible and AVS - Address Verification Service). Worldpay Ltd is a secure, online, real-time payment service provider, supporting all major credit and debit cards with the (major) UK acquiring banks for Visa, Mastercard, Switch, Solo, Delta, JCB, American Express and Diners Club.  
We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you. 

We will keep you informed of the progress of your order by email. We will send you an email confirming your order and another email when it is processed, cancelled or completed. 

_Surveys or Contests_  
From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information such as name and shipping address, and demographic information such as postcode.

We use this information to notify contest winners and award prizes, to monitor site traffic or personalise the site (in the case of anonymous information collected in surveys), to send participants an email newsletter. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties.

_Tell-A-Friend_  
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. SEO does not store this information and only uses it for sole purpose of sending this one-time email.  
**  
Uses of Information**  
We may use the personally identifying information you provide for any of the following purposes (1) to fulfil orders; (2) to fulfil prizes; (3) to respond to specific requests from customers; (4) to send you emails and regarding your order status; (5) if you subscribe to our newsletter, to send you our newsletter.

We use the non-personally identifying information collected by site to understand the use of our site and make improvements.

At times, we may conduct online surveys to better understand the needs and profiles of our visitors. When we conduct a survey, we will try to let you know how we will use the information at the time we collect the information from you on the Internet. In accordance with the Privacy & Electronic Communications Act we do not send random marketing emails to personal email addresses (spam).

**Communications from the Site**

_Special Offers and Updates_  
We will occasionally send you information on products, special deals and promotions. You can sign up for these emails from us on our registration page.

Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out.

_Newsletters_  
If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter, we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe. Please see the Choice and Opt-out section.

_Customer Service_  
Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**  
_Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)_  
We DO NOT share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our partners and advertisers. This information does not identify individual users. We do not link aggregate user data with personally identifiable information. 

_Personally identifiable information_  
We DO NOT Share Personally Identifiable Information with Third Parties 

_Legal Disclaimer_  
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

**Choice/Opt-out**  
We provide you the opportunity to opt-out of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, if you purchase a service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference on our registration form by not subscribing to our newsletter.

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or by emailing us at [ ](http://www.searchengineoptimising.com/%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20var%20prefix%20=%20'ma'%20+%20'il'%20+%20'to';%20var%20path%20=%20'hr'%20+%20'ef'%20+%20'=';%20var%20addy37807%20=%20'sales'%20+%20'@';%20addy37807%20=%20addy37807%20+%20'searchengineoptimising'%20+%20'.'%20+%20'com';%20document.write\(%20'%3Ca%20'%20+%20path%20+%20'/''%20+%20prefix%20+%20':'%20+%20addy37807%20+%20'/'%3E'%20\);%20document.write\(%20addy37807%20\);%20document.write\(%20'%3C//a%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E/n%20%3C/script%3E%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\(%20'%3Cspan%20style=/'display:%20none;/'%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3EThis%20e-mail%20address%20is%20being%20protected%20from%20spam%20bots,%20you%20need%20JavaScript%20enabled%20to%20view%20it%20%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\(%20'%3C/'%20\);%20document.write\(%20'span%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E)[sales@searchengineoptimising.com](mailto:sales@searchengineoptimising.com). We offer an opportunity to opt-out of newsletters on your account information pages, or you may contact us at the address below to opt-out.

You will be notified when your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party.

**Log Files**  
As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. 

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyse trends, to administer the site, to track users movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. 

We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information. 

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a users computer for record-keeping purposes. We do not use cookies on this site but may in the future. We will not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. 

We use do not use session ID cookies or persistent cookies but may in the future. We could use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser file. 

We may set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don't have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site.

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. See Third Party Security Services.

**Third Party Security Services**  
The Hacker Safe logo appearing on this Web site is delivered to users by ScanAlert, Inc., our security partner. We share web site usage information about users this reputable third party ScanAlert, Inc for the sole purpose of ensuring our site is as secure as possible. 

ScanAlert, Inc uses cookies. The information that ScanAlert, Inc collects and shares through this technology is not personally identifiable. 

For more information about our third-party advertiser, [click here to view ScanAlert's current privacy statement.](http://www.hackersafe.com/Content.sa?page=privacy)

**Links to Other Sites**  
This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by SEO. Please be aware that we, SEO, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. 

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. 

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site. 

**Access to Personally Identifiable Information**

We conform to the requirements of the Data Protection Act, 1998. Our Data Protection Registration number is Z9225225.

You have a right to access the personal data that is held about you. If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by making the change on your account information page, by emailing our Customer Support at [sales@searchengineoptimising.com](mailto:sales@feelconfident.co.uk), by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. 

**Security**  
The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter personal information (such as your name and address) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). Our website utilises a 128-bit SSL certificates thereby offering the highest level of encryption or security possible. This means you can rest assured that communications between your browser and this site's web servers are private and secure.

This site is tested and certified daily to pass the FBI/SANS Internet Security Test. The "live" HACKER SAFE mark appears only when a web site's security meets the highest security scanning standards of the U.S. government, Visa, MasterCard, American Express, Discover and JCB.. 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, however we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at [sales@feelconfident.co.uk](mailto:sales@feelconfident.co.uk).

**Business Transitions**  
In the event SEO goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email and a prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

**Changes in this Privacy Statement**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

**Contact Us**  
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:   
SEO  
2 Richill Park  
Londonderry  
BT47 5QX 

Tel: 0871 711 9714  
Fax: 0870 622 0097   
Email: [sales@searchengineoptimising.com](mailto:sales@searchengineoptimising.com)  
Web: [www.](http://www.feelconfident.co.uk/)[searchengineoptimising.com](http://www.searchengineoptimising.com/)
